Guide to the Frank T. Wood papers, 1930-1993.
Wood, Frank T. papers, 1930-1993.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Frank T. Wood papers, 1930-1993.
4865
Frank T. Wood
3.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, photographs, topical files, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, photographs, topical files, and other material of a Syracuse, New York social welfare leader; also includes family papers and photographs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, photographs, topical files, and other material of a Syracuse, New York social welfare leader; includes family papers and photographs. Subjects include African-American social and political life, literature programs in Africa, black fraternal orders, Republican politics, and other matters of social welfare. Also, transcripts of an interview with Peggy Wood.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Wood, Frank T.; Wood, Peggy.; National Republican Party--New York (State)--Syracuse.
Subjects:
Public welfare--New York (State)--Syracuse.; Social service--New York (State)--Syracuse.; Afro-Americans--New York (State)--Syracuse.; Literacy--Africa.; Friendly societies--Afro-American.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal papers
Boxes 1, 3-4
Series II. Correspondence
Box 1
Series III. Speeches and notes
Box 1
Series IV. Subject files
Boxes 1-2
Series V. Episcopal Church, Diocese of Central New York
Box 2, 5
Series VI. Peggy Wood Interviews
Box 6
CONTAINER LIST
- Personal papers
  - Correspondence, 1938-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1957-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Frank Wood, Jr. and Family (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings about Frank Wood, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 9-12)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Friends anf Family (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Awards and Certificates (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - Selected Financial Records (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Notebook, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Pocket Diaries, 1954-1986 (Box 3)
  - Charcoal Drawing of Cape Cod by P. Wood, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings (Box 4)
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1976 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 37-39)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 49-50)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Speeches and notes
  - Speeches (Box 1, Folder 52-58)
  - Remarks by Frank T. Wood (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
- Subject files
  - Africa Postcards (Box 1, Folder 59-61)
  - Africa Souvenirs (Box 1, Folder 62-63)
  - Afrolit Files (Box 4)
  - Afrolit Seminar, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Alpha Phi Omega Fraternity (Box 1, Folder 65-66)
  - AAA (Triple A) Automobile Club of Syracuse (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - BIDCO (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Black Power Caucus (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Black Voters and the Republican Party (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Central District (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Character and Spiritual Education (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Crusade for Opportunity (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Funerals (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Housing/Segregation Issues (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Interracial Fellowship Scholarship Committee (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
  - Juvenile Protection Workshop (Box 2, Folder 5-8)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. - First Public Holiday, Jan. 20, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NAAPC (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers, Inc. - Legislation (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
  - New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers, Inc. - Convention (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Onondaga County Inspector of Elections, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Onondaga County Population (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Political (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Political Science Paper (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Public Affairs Committee (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - School Reorganization (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Small Buisness Leadership Assistance Center, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Training, Jobs, Education - Urban Renewal - Newark (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Unemployment/Job Discrimination (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - United Negro College Fund (UNFC) (Box 2, Folder 24-27)
  - UNFC Committee, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Urban Affairs (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Urban Crisis (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - White House Conference on Youth (Box 2, Folder 31-35)
  - Y.O.U. Group Leaders (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Miscellany (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Miscellany (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Episcopal Church, Diocese of Central New York
  - Episcopal Church Hunger Committee (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Bread for the World, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
  - Episcopal Diocese of Central New York, Food and Famine Committee (Box 2, Folder 40-42)
  - General Convention of the Episcopal Church: Commission on the Structure of the Church (Box 2, Folder 43-45)
  - Commission on the Structure of the Church, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Commission on the Structure of the Church, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 47-48)
  - Commission on the Structure of the Church, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Commission on the Structure of the Church, Report Drafts, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Commission on the Structure of the Church, Report Drafts, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Episcopal Church - 62nd General Convention (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Grace Episcopal Church (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Poems and Prayers (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Project REAP (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Diocese of Central New York - Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - The Role of the Presiding Bishop Report, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 57-60)
  - Episcopal Church Hunger Committee, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Church Issues & Documents (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Peggy Wood
  - Transripts of interviews with Peggy Wood, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1-11)
  - 15 MC60 and XB60 Microcassettes - Interviews with Peggy Wood, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)